*I love to live alone*
*我就喜欢一个人住*
*'cause I'm in my cleaning zone*
*可以随意打扫卫生*
Gabi, hi!
加比  你好
How are you? How's Switzerland?
你怎么样  瑞士好不好
Have you learned how to yodel yet?
源自瑞士阿尔卑斯山区的唱法
You ask me that every week
你每个星期都要问我一次
and the answer is still no-de-lay-hee-hoo!
而答案仍然是  木有嘞哦嘞
Gets me every time.
每次都戳到我笑点
Wait a minute. It's not Sunday night.
等会儿  今天又不是礼拜天晚上
Why are you calling me now?
你为什么现在跟我视频
I just missed ya.
我就是想你了
How did flambe week go?
法式料理  在食物上浇烈酒并点火
Fla-mazing.
太热辣了
I learned how to make a peppercorn steak with brandy,
我学会了怎么用白兰地做黑椒牛排
how to burn down a restaurant,
怎么烧毁餐厅
how to make Crepe Suzette...
怎么做橘子黄油薄饼
Wait, wait. Back up.
等会儿  倒回去一点
So, the secret is actually lemon zest...
秘诀就在于柠檬皮屑
Back it up a little more.
再多倒一点
Something about burning a restaurant down?
我好像听见了烧毁餐厅什么的
Yeah. There may have been a teeny-tiny major fire.
是啊  起了一丁丁点的大火啦
The French alcohol that I was using
我用的法国酒度数
was a little higher proof than I realized.
比我想象的高了一点
I blame the metric system.
都怪欧洲人用公制
Did they?
别人也这么觉得吗
No, they blamed me.
不  他们怪我
Oh, you poor thing. What are you gonna do?
好可怜  你打算怎么办
Come home?
回家呗
Oh, my god! You're here!
天啊  你回来了
They kicked me out.
他们把我赶走了
Aw, you okay?
你还好吗
No-de-lay-hee-hoo!
不好嘞哦嘞
Well, overall, it sounds like you had a great time.
总体来说  你还玩得挺爽的
But don't you think
但你觉得我们
we should talk about the elephant in the room?
是不是应该谈谈最明显的问题
Yes, Sofia, listen, I'm going to get a job
是的  索菲亚  我会找到工作
and I'm going to be able to pay rent.
然后就可以付房租了
- I promise. - No, I was talking about Josh.
-我保证  -不  我说的是乔什
Oh, that elephant.
这个问题啊
So, what's your plan?
那你打算怎么办
It's funny you should ask.
幸亏你问起
I was gonna go to his place straight from the airport,
我本来打算直接从机场去他家
I was going to look him right in the eye and say,
望着他的眼睛  说
"The way that I left was hurtful and horrible
"我当时就那么走了  真是很残酷无情
and I am so, so sorry.
非常非常抱歉
Can you ever forgive me?"
你能不能原谅我"
- Well, why didn't you? - I got scared.
-你怎么没说  -我好怕怕
When I was in Switzerland, I tried reaching out.
我在瑞士的时候  试过联系他
I called him and I texted him.
给他打了电话  还发了短信
But then I felt like I should just leave him alone.
但后来又觉得好像不该烦他
-Why? -'Cause he wrote back, "Leave me alone."
-为什么  -因为他回我说"别烦我"
But now that I'm home, I really want to see him.
但现在我回家了  很想见他
But why? Because you feel guilty?
为什么  因为你觉得内疚
Because you want to apologize?
还是你想道歉
You still have feelings for him?
还是你仍然喜欢他
Yes, yes, and I don't know.
是  是  我也不知道
Oh, my god!
天啊
Do you think that I subconsciously burnt down that restaurant
你觉得我是不是下意识地烧了餐厅
so that I could come home early and see him?
好早点回来见他
No!
当然不是
And that is what you will tell the police and everyone.
你对警察和其他人也得这么说
I still can't believe
我真不敢相信
you're controlling that with your phone.
你能用手机控制它
Yeah. With my app,
是啊  我的应用
you can control it with any phone.
可以用任何一部手机遥控无人机
It's kind of like a universal TV remote,
就好像是个万能电视遥控器
but for drones.
不过遥控的是无人机
Two things that everyone loves.
两件人人都爱的事
Drones and people always on their phones.
无人机和一直拿着手机
I want to buy it.
我要买
Like I told you before, the app isn't for sale.
跟你说过了  这个应用不卖的
Well, here's something new.
那我说点新鲜的吧
How about I buy your whole company?
我买了你的整个公司如何
Not interested.
没兴趣
- I'll give you half a billion dollars. - Interested.
-我出价五亿美元  -太感兴趣了
Yolanda, if Josh sells his company to Kal,
尤兰达  如果乔什把公司卖给卡尔
I will be the publicist
那我就会是
to one of the richest men in San Francisco.
旧金山富豪之一的公关啦
And I'll be washing the underpants
而我就要给
of one of the richest men in San Francisco.
旧金山富豪之一洗内裤啦
Yours sounds better.
还是你的比较好听
Josh is about to hit it big
乔什会卖个好价钱的
and his whole team will share the glory.
他的整个团队都会跟着沾光
Except you.
除了你
You're new.
你是新来的
No one cares about you.
没人在乎你
Who hurt you?
谁伤害你了
I'll get it! This is the best day ever.
我去开门  今天是最美好的日子
Hi!
你好
Oh, my god! It returned!
天啊  它回来了
Go away!
走开
Please, Elliot.
快开门  艾略特
I just need to talk to Josh.
我只是想和乔什谈谈
No! You will never set foot in this house again...
不行  你再也不许进这个门了
Oh, my damn, Gabi! Come on in!
神啊  加比  快进来
No, Yolanda! I forbid it.
不行  尤兰达  我不允许
Forbid this.
不你个头
- Gabi? - Hey, Josh.
-加比  -你好  乔什
Is it me or did it just get awkward in here?
是我觉得  还是气氛真的变尴尬了
You're back early.
你早回来了
Yeah, about that.
是啊  这个...
Listen, I kinda wanted to talk to you about something.
听着  我有事想和你谈谈
Elliot, maybe we shouldn't stand here and watch this.
艾略特  我们或许不该在这儿看着
You're right. Let's stand over there.
说得对  我们挪那儿去吧
If this is about your job,
如果你是想要回工作
I actually hired a new chef.
我已经雇了个新的厨师
Yeah, I know, Yolanda told me.
是啊  我知道  尤兰达告诉我了
Here she is. Adriana.
就是她  阿德里亚娜
This is Gabi, my ex-- chef--
这位是加比  我的前任...厨师
ex-chef.
前任厨师
Oh, you're Gabi.
你就是加比
Or as Elliot calls you,
或者是艾略特说的
"She who must not be named."
"那个连名字都不能提的人"
- Pleased to meet you. - Very nice to meet you.
-很高兴认识你  -很高兴
So, is now a good time for us to--
现在是不是可以...
Never! He doesn't want to talk to you!
不行  他不想跟你谈
Is that true, Josh? Do you not want to talk to me?
真的吗乔什  你不想跟我谈吗
Of course he wants to talk to you!
他当然想跟你谈
He's got a lot of feelings he needs to let out!
他有一肚子话想对你说
Because I have feelings that I need to let out, too.
我也有一肚子话想对你说
Starting with I'm sorry.
第一句就是  对不起
You can save your apology! He has moved on!
省省你的道歉吧  他已经翻篇了
The hell he has!
翻篇个鬼
Yolanda, stay out of it!
尤兰达  别多管闲事
Stop!
停
You! You! Out!
你  你  出去
Someone's wound a little tight!
有人被戳到痛处了
Look, Elliot's right.
艾略特说得对
You don't need to apologize to me.
你没必要跟我道歉
I've moved on. Everything's cool.
我已经翻篇了  我很好
In case you were wondering, a seagull ate your dessert, not me.
别误会  吃你甜点的是只海鸥  不是我
I better be off.
我该走了
Kal, this is my former chef Gabi.
卡尔  这是我的前任厨师加比
She just got back
她刚从瑞士
from a really fancy apprenticeship in Switzerland.
一个很棒的培训班学成归来
Ooh, an apprenticeship in Europe. You must be good.
欧洲的培训班  你一定很厉害
I'm looking for a chef. Are you interested?
我正想招一个厨师  你有兴趣吗
- Excuse me? - Excuse me?
-你说什么  -你说什么
I'm sorry. We haven't been properly introduced.
对不起  我们还没正式介绍
I just moved in next door. I'm Kal. I'm a billionaire.
我刚搬到隔壁  我叫卡尔  是个亿万富翁
Next door?
隔壁吗
Listen, Josh, the last thing I want to do
听着乔什  我不想让你
is make you feel awkward.
觉得太尴尬
What? Me? No. You! Awkward! Me? What?
啥  我  不  你  尴尬  我  怎么会
Look, we had a little thing before she left.
她走之前我们有点小误会
Actually, we didn't. We almost did.
实际上也没什么事  差不多而已
Well, I really don't want to get into the middle of a thing.
我可不想掺合进什么事里
There was no thing. Did you not just hear me?
没事  你没听我说吗
No thing happened.
什么事都没有
And since there was no thing,
既然没什么事
there's nothing to get in the middle of.
也就没什么掺合不掺合的
Just a bunch of-- air.
全都是...浮云
So, you're cool if I take the job?
那你不介意我接受这工作吧
Cool! Me! What? Yes! Cool! Me! Yeah! Job. Take.
介意  我  什么  当然不  工作  接吧
- You're sure? - I mean, is no one hearing what I'm saying?
-你确定吗  -到底有没有人在听我说话
Is this thing on? Take the job.
话筒没开吗  接吧
Okay. I guess I'll take it. Thank you.
好吧  那我接受  谢谢你
Great! Can you start right away?
太好了  你可以立即上岗吗
I've got a very important business dinner tomorrow night,
我明晚有个非常重要的商务晚宴
and I really have to impress the guy.
必须要能打动对方
Oh, who's the guy?
那人是谁
Me.
在下
I still can't believe it.
我还是不敢相信
Only you would get a job
只有你能找到
that just so happens to be across the hall from the elephant.
正好在"问题"家对面的工作
I know! But I asked the elephant a hundred times
我知道  但是我问了他一百次
and he said he was cool with it.
他都说不介意
So what am I supposed to do? I need a job.
我该怎么办  我需要一份工作
Well, on that note, take a seat.
既然那样  请坐
Sofia, I don't need one of your pep talks
索菲亚  我不需要你打鸡血
that's actually a lecture.
那跟听讲座没啥区别
Oh! But you do.
但是你真的需要
This new job is a fresh start.
这个新工作是个崭新的开始
So, to help you stay on track,
为了保证你步入正轨
I've put together a little list of "dos and don'ts".
我整理了一张《要和不要做》清单
"Do act professional.
"要表现得专业
"Don't have sex with your boss.
不要跟你老板上床
"Do wear pants.
要穿裤子
Don't take them off."
不要脱下来"
Sofia, I'm not gonna sleep with--
索菲亚  我没有要跟...
"Do prepare a delicious dinner tonight for Kal and Josh.
"要为卡尔和乔什准备美味的晚餐
"Don't engage with Josh. Don't look at him.
不要跟乔什订婚  不要看他
Don't talk about the past. Don't talk about the future."
不要谈论过去  不要谈论未来"
- But what if-- - Don't.
-那如果...  -不要
- But what if he-- - Don't.
-那如果他...  -不要
Okay, fine. You're right, Sofia.
好吧  你说得对  索菲亚
Man, how did I ever make it in switzerland without you?
没有你我在瑞士是怎么挺过来的啊
You didn't.
你没挺过来
You burned down a restaurant.
你烧了一间餐厅
Oh, my god. Gabi, this looks amazing.
天呐  加比  这太不可思议了
Well, your place is amazing.
你这本来装修就很好
I especially love the piano.
我特别喜欢那架钢琴
- Is it a grand? - Oh, it cost way more than that.
-是三角钢琴吗  -它可不止三角钱
Listen, Kal, I just want you to know
卡尔  我想让你知道
that tonight's dinner with Josh
今晚跟乔什的晚餐
is going to be completely professional.
会非常的专业
- Why wouldn't it be? - It would be.
-为什么会不专业  -不会的
That's Josh.
乔什来了
I'm going to go in the other room.
我要去里屋等着
Could you announce me how they do on Downton Abbey?
你一会能像《唐顿庄园》里那样介绍我吗
Yes.
可以
Okay. Be professional. Don't talk about the past.
好了  专业一点  不谈过去
Don't talk about the future.
不谈未来
We need to talk.
我们谈谈吧
Gabi, this is a really important night.
加比  今晚真的很重要
I know! For me, too!
我知道  对我来说也是
We finally have a chance to talk.
我们终于有机会谈谈了
I'm talking about the deal with Kal.
我要跟卡尔谈生意
This is really important to me.
这个对我真的很重要
But I know that you're feeling things.
但我知道你对我有感情
Like annoyed?
比如...讨厌吗
Good. That's good. Go on.
对  很好  继续
Look, I meant what I said yesterday.
我昨天说的都是真心话
I'm cool with you working here,
你在这工作我不介意
so can you please just act professional?
所以你能不能表现得专业一点
Fine! Can I get you a glass of wine, sir?
好吧  您要喝酒吗  先生
No, thank you. $500 million deals and alcohol do not mix well.
不  谢谢  五亿美元的生意可得谨慎
I was waiting to be announced,
我本来想等你介绍
but how long can a man hide behind his own door?
但一个男人又能躲在门后多久呢
Sorry. May I please introduce--
抱歉  现在有请...
The moment passed.
时机已经过了
- Hello, Josh. - Good to see you, Kal.
-你好  乔什  -你好  卡尔
Before we get started,
开始之前
there's something personal I wanted to discuss with you.
我有件私事想和你讨论下
Sure, what is it?
好的  什么事
All right. I'll get right down to it.
我就直说了
I'm hot for your chef.
我对你的厨师有意思
I hope it's not a problem.
希望你不介意
Problem?
介意吗
Hell no, it's great!
才不介意  多好
She's fantastic.
她太棒了
I know we only just met,
我知道我们才认识
But we've got the most amazing connection.
但真的特别有默契
I love it! It's fun. Fun news.
很好  这消息真有趣
Great! I'm going to ask her out
好  等吃完晚餐
as soon as we're finished with dinner.
我就准备约她出去
Okay, the first course is ready.
好  头盘准备好了
This looks divine.
看起来真美味
Gabi, you're a godsend.
加比  你真是上帝的恩赐
I can't believe you let me steal her away from you.
难以置信你居然让我挖走她
It's not stealing when she wasn't even working for me.
她已经没替我工作了  不算挖
Gabi, more wine?
加比  再倒点酒
- Oh, I thought you-- - More wine!
-我以为你...  -倒
Gabi, your oyster is perfection.
该词暗指女性私处
I'm so glad you like it.
真高兴你喜欢
There's plenty more where that came from.
还有很多呢
All right! You know what? I don't need this big fancy dinner.
够了  你猜怎么着  我不用吃这顿大餐
I've had Gabi's oysters.
我也吃过加比的生蚝
Do you have the initial offer for me to sign?
把初始报价合同给我签字吧
A man who knows what he wants.
目的很明确哈
All right. Let's get down to biz-natch.
好  我们来谈生意
Now feel free to take your time and look over--
你可以仔细看下合同...
No. Blah, blah, blah. Lots of zeros.
不用  废话废话  一堆零
All looks in order. Signing.
看起来不错  签字了
Letter of intent off to the attorney's.
意向书送给律师过目
Great doing biz-natch with you.
很高兴和你做生意
Cheerio! Tut-tut! Must be off!
再见  拜拜  我走了
May I now introduce the second course--
下面呈上第二道...
You've never seen Downton Abbey, have you?
你根本没看过《唐顿庄园》  是不是
No.
是的
I'm going to ask her to hang out tonight.
我今晚准备约她出去
Hey, Kal, guess what?
卡尔  你猜怎么着
I don't care!
我不在乎
Champagne! Like that's going to impress her.
香槟  好像这能打动她一样
Holy cow, I think it did!
妈呀  还真有用
Is it too soon to go to the bedroom?
这就去卧室  太快了吧
No!
不
Wait! Adriana?
等等  阿德里亚娜吗
Oh, no! No, no, no! No, no, no!
不  不要  不要
Ohh, drone down! We have a drone down!
坠毁  无人机坠毁了
Thank you!
谢谢
Good first day?
第一天怎么样
You' will be happy to know, I kept my pants on.
你会很满意的  我没脱裤子
Here's to baby steps.
敬你的循序渐进
Kal was great. I had no problem with Kal.
卡尔人很好  我们很融洽
But when Josh showed up for his business dinner,
但乔什来参加商务晚宴时
he wouldn't talk to me.
不愿跟我说话
I tried to get him to talk to me, but he just wouldn't.
我想让他跟我谈谈  他就是不干
And then he was all like, "Tut-tut. Cheerio. I must be off".
然后说"拜拜  再见  我走了"
Why are you looking at me like that?
你干嘛那样看着我
It's just-- all your stupid, crazy, drama--
就是你这愚蠢  爱演的样子
I missed you!
我好想你
Come on. I'm not all stupid, crazy drama.
我不是光愚蠢又爱演的
Gabi, open the door quick! Gabi! Gabi! Gabi!
加比  快开门  加比
I flew a drone into Kal's penthouse and I crashed it
我把无人机飞进卡尔家里  现在坠毁了
and I need you to get it back for me.
需要你去帮我拿回来
I can't believe I thought learning to knit could fill this void.
不敢相信我还觉得学织毛衣就不空虚了
Okay, what are you talking about?
好吧  你在说什么
Look, gabi, I need you to get that drone back for me.
加比  我需要你去把那架无人机拿回来
I could lose $500 million.
我会损失五个亿的
- Okay, I'll help you. - Great. Let's go.
-好吧  我帮你  -太好了  我们走
If--
如果...
if you agree to have a talk when we're done.
如果你同意拿回来以后谈谈
A real talk. A feelings talk.
情真意切地谈谈
- Do you have the key to Kal's apartment? - Yes.
-你有卡尔家钥匙吗  -有
Feelings talk it is. Let's go.
那就情真意切地谈谈  走
I think the drone is over by the piano.
无人机应该在钢琴边上
Okay. Wait here.
好  等一下
Josh, I got it.
乔什  找到了
That's a roomba.
那是地宝
A vacuum.
吸尘器
Now would be a good time to tell you,
现在是告诉你的时候了
I don't know what a drone looks like.
我不知道无人机长什么样
It's a quad copter with four rotors.
是带四个螺旋桨的小飞机
Four rotors! Why didn't you say so?
四个螺旋桨啊  你不早说
What the hell? Kal!
什么声音  卡尔
What-- what am I doing in here?
我怎么会在这里
Is the question you're probably asking.
你可能想这么问吧
Gabi, I know you're looking for Josh's drone.
加比  我知道你在找乔什的无人机
Oh, that's a drone!
无人机长这样啊
Yep, you caught me. That's what I'm here for.
被你抓住了  我是来找这个的
But not because he put me up to it.
但不是因为他让我来的
I'm here completely on my own-- with Josh.
我是一个人...和乔什来的
Josh, what the hell is this doing in my apartment?
乔什  你们在我家里搞什么
Kal, I can explain everything.
卡尔  听我解释
The drone's artificial intelligence is too advanced.
这无人机的人工智能技术太先进了
This could be the start of a robot uprising.
或许是机器人起义的开端
Cut the crap. Why are you spying on me?
别乱扯  你为什么要监视我
Kal, I'm not spying on you.
卡尔  我不是在监视你
What's going on out here?
外面怎么回事
Adriana?
阿德里亚娜
I think the question is what's going on in there, sexy robe?
该问的是你穿着那性感睡袍怎么回事吧
Oh, I get it.
我明白了
I knew you were bothered when I asked if I could date your chef.
我就知道你介意我跟你厨师约会
You were spying on Adriana.
你在监视阿德里亚娜
Wait, Kal, you asked Josh if you could date his chef?
等等  卡尔  你问乔什能不能跟他厨师约会
Did you think he meant me chef and not she chef?
你以为他说的是我  不是她吗
What?
什么
I know what's going on here. Listen, he wasn't spying on you.
我知道怎么回事了  他没有监视你
He was spying on me.
是在监视我
I don't care who he was spying on.
我不在乎他监视谁
The point is he was spying!
重点是他监视人
I need to trust the people that I work with.
我要信任自己合作的人
The deal is off. And you, you're fired.
生意吹了  你被解雇了
- What?  - What?
-什么  -什么
But what about my perfect oyster?
但你还说我的生蚝很完美
But who's gonna cook for you?
那谁来帮你做饭
Actually, I'm going to.
实际上  我准备来
Josh, I'm sorry, I quit.
乔什  对不起  我辞职了
I'm going to go work for Kal now.
现在准备为卡尔工作
Wait a minute. You're going to cook for the same guy
等等  你要替跟你上床的人
you're sleeping with?
工作吗
Girl, I have a dos and don'ts list for you.
姑娘  我可有张清单要送你
Well, thanks a lot, you just got me fired!
真是多谢  你让我被解雇了
Yeah, well, you just cost me a $500 million deal!
是啊  你还砸了我五亿美元的生意呢
Me? Me? That was you.
我吗  分明是你自己
- That was all you! - Oh, whatever!
-都怪你  -随便了
Okay. Deal's a deal. Time to talk.
行了  我们说好的  该谈谈了
Okay. I'm upset.
好  我很伤心
I think my drone's broken. And now you know how I feel.
我的无人机碎了  你还知道了我的感受
What the hell is the matter with you?
你到底是怎么回事
When I first got back, you said you'd moved on. You were good.
我才回来时  你说你放下了  不介意了
And now, all of a sudden you're spying on me
现在  突然又开始监视我
because you think I'm sleeping with your neighbor?
因为觉得我在和你邻居上床
What is that all about?
这都是怎么回事
Do you really want to know what that's all about
你真想知道这都是怎么回事吗
or are you just gonna jump on another plane
还是又准备一遇到难题
when things get too difficult?
就坐飞机跑路
So you are mad.
所以你是在生气
You pulled the rug out from under me, Gabi!
你把我一个人晾在这  加比
You left me like a smiling idiot at Elliot's engagement party!
让我在艾略特的订婚派对上像个傻子
I told you I loved you, I kissed you,
我跟你说了爱你  吻了你
and I know that meant something to you.
我也知道这对你有意义
- It did. - Then why would you leave me like that?
-是的  -那你为什么还让我那样
Because--
因为...
Josh, if I saw you then I wouldn't have been able to go.
乔什  如果我看到你  就走不掉了
When I first left, I kept asking myself
第一次离开时  我一直扪心自问
how I could leave when we were just getting started.
怎么才要在一起了我就要走
And what did you come up with?
那你问出什么了
Because I couldn't come up with anything.
因为我可什么理由都想不到
Being with you would have been too easy.
跟你在一起太简单了
This is easy?
现在这样简单吗
Josh.
乔什
You would move mountains to make me happy.
为哄我高兴你可以移山开路
And I want to move my own mountains. Does that make any sense?
但我想自己移山  你懂我的意思吗
I know what mountains are.
我知道山是什么
I went to Switzerland because I want to be the next Julia Child.
我去瑞士  是因为想做下一个茱莉亚·蔡尔德
And if you did everything for me,
如果你什么事都帮我做了
then I would lose my own drive to make that dream come true.
那我就失去了实现梦想的动力
Do you understand that?
你明白吗
I know what dreams are.
我知道梦想是什么
Josh...
乔什
Look, Gabi--
加比
when you left, it was horrible.
你离开以后  事情很糟
I was a mess.
我不知所措
So I threw myself into work--
所以全心投入工作
and-- actually it kinda got me to a place
然后...实际上差点做成了
where I almost made $500 million.
五亿美元的大生意
So, me leaving was a good thing?
所以  我离开是好事吗
Yeah. My accountant thinks you should ruin my life more often.
没错  我的会计师觉得你该多毁掉我的生活
But, Gabi...
但是...加比
I can't go through that again.
我不能再经历这事了
Josh, I am sorry. I am really, truly, very, very sorry.
乔什  对不起  真的真的对不起
And you for...
你会原...
I forgive you, Gabi.
我原谅你  加比
Josh, you did not have to say that.
乔什  你不用这么大度的
So, where do we go from here?
那我们现在怎么办
How about we go back to doing what we do best?
不如做回我们最擅长的事吧
- Being friends. - I would love that.
-朋友  -我很赞成
Me, too.
我也是
- So, we're good? - We're very good.
-那我们没事了吗  -没事了
Good. Feelings talk adjourned.
好了  情真意切的谈话结束
All right. I got to get out of here.
我走了
I gotta get up early and start the job search.
还要早起去找工作呢
Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
天啊  天啊
Oh, my god. Oh, my god. Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
天啊  天啊  天啊
Oh, my god. Oh, my god. Oh, my god. What?
天什么呀
I can't believe I'm about to say this.
不敢相信我居然要说这话
What?
什么
- Do you want... - Yes!
-你想...  -想
- ...your old job back? - Yes!
-继续干吗  -想
Yes, I do, thank you! Thank you! Thank you!
我想  谢谢  谢谢
Now I don't have to get up early.
现在我就不用早起啦
Thanks for the feelings talk.
谢谢你情真意切的谈话
What are friends for?
这不就是朋友该干的嘛
- See you tomorrow, chef. - See you tomorrow, boss.
-明天见  大厨  -明天见  老板
Elliot, I have some news.
艾略特  我有事要说
The deal with Kal's off.
和卡尔的交易泡汤了
Damn it! All that money!
讨厌  那么多钱呢
Okay, well, I'll just be the publicist
好吧  那我就只当
to another cutest guy in San Francisco.
旧金山帅哥之一的公关好了
I have some other news--
还有些别的事...
Adriana quit.
阿德里亚娜辞职了
- Good morning. - No!
-早上好  -不要啊
It lives! No!
它还活着  不要